[Music]
The C and C levels we're doing in
places like Germany and
Singapore have to do with
relationships. How to change the future of your
relationships. It can be
business relationships, it can be relationships with your
partner. I gave a great lesson on
business in southern
China, in a big city called
[Music]
G, which is outside of Hong
Kong. All the things, the objects you see
in the world are made in
GCH. Most of the things in this
room over there—the chair, the
carpet, the paint, the lights, your clothes—
everything is made in
GCH. It's like one big
factory, like hundreds of
kilometers of
factories. So, of course, they're
very tough business people
because all the big companies
in the world go
there and have contact with all the
companies. They're fighting with
them. So,
the people there are very tough,
and they're very
intelligent. So,
we had business meetings for
days, and at the end of it all, one of the
women raised her
hand and said, "You're teaching us
the principles of doing business, making
money. We have
[Music]
money. Can I use these same
principles to find a good
partner?" I said
[Music] yes,
and she said, "And you can use these..."  Principles
to fix the couple you
have, you can fix your
husband, a man raised his
hand, you can fix your wife too, you can also,
that's level C,
and in the future we're going to do that, those are
levels, we're doing
now these two nights in Buenos
Aires and the TR retreat,
many people came up to me and
said, I don't know what to do with my life, I
have a
problem. For example, they tell me, I
graduated from
university, then at the end of
university there's a lot of
pressure, your dad, your uncle, everyone's going to say, "
Well, now you're going to do, you're going to do, I do
n't know." It
was university, four years, we're
paying for
university, now you're graduating
next week, what are you going to do?
Well, you have to pay us
back, pay us back, you have to
decide now what you
want in this country, but in the United States
there's a lot of pressure right now
at the end of
university to tell your parents and
your
uncle, say, "I'm going to do this, I'm going to do that, I'm going
to be a
lawyer, I'm going to be a
doctor, I'm going to be a
scientist." The last one would seem like it
was the last week of university, you have to
Deciding what you're going to
do in the United States is like the
end of the stage where you're under
your parents' care.
After that moment, they don't have to
pay anything else for
you. A week after university, you're supposed to
have a
job and
write a
thesis. It's not
for before the
doctorate. At my university, everyone
is very
nervous. It's due
next week. It's
supposed to be months.
No, I can't.
One of my
classmates finished his
thesis and went to give it to the
professor. He put it on the
professor's desk. At my school, my university,
like the building, has many
towers. This classmate walked to the
top of a tower and
jumped and
died. He was so crazy with all this
pressure from his
parents. Next week you have to
start making
money. Next week you have to
decide what you're going to do for the
rest of your
life. Many of us
graduate, and our parents are like, "What are you going to
do?" Find a job.
Next week you go to many
places, you try to find a
job. The first job they offer you, you take it
because you feel so much
pressure. Maybe it's because you're  Secretary
in an
office, you take this
job,
I think work is like a
drug because it starts to change your
mind, then you start to get addicted to
this
job, and then you meet someone at
work. You meet
someone and you get married, then
children, then children, you need more
money, you look for a
different job, your mind starts to slow down, I have to
stay
here now, I have children, now I have a
house. Maybe I can move up a
little in this same
company, your whole life, so it's about
your children, your
house, and starting to believe
those desires.
[Music]
boss, I'm not doing what I want to
do, my life was
stolen,
years, I don't even know what I
wanted to do,
but now it's too
late, you're trapped in the
job, you're trapped in the
family, that situation now sticks to you
and you don't have any
choice. Many people are like that, many
people have
approached me. I've been in the United States for 40
years. Right now,
due
to the
country's economy, many people have lost their
jobs. They were, for example, assistants to
a boss for 20
years. One day they came to work and were
told, "Go back home, we don't
need you anymore."
And people  It's like, "And now what am I going to
do?" So I think you have like two
types of
people.
Some of them are around 20
or
25 years old, trying to figure out what to do with their lives. They do
n't know what to do with their
lives. Other people are
different. They're 20
years old, they found a job, got
married, have
kids,
and they don't know what to
do. Suddenly they woke up and said, "I don't
know if I wanted to do
this." And then there's another type of
person who's like 50
years old, who had a
family, and the kids
grew up, went to college, and
then
left. And now suddenly the house is like, "It's
too
big." I have a lot of friends
like that. They built a really
big house because they had three
kids, and the kids
grew up, and the kids said, "We're leaving. I don't
need the house anymore."
Some parents beg them to stay: "
Bring your wife here,
live with us, get married, live with
us all together
here." The kid is smart and says, "No
[Music]
thanks," because his mom is going to tell him what to
do. So suddenly, as the
kids
leave and the house
empties, they
always say, "Let's maintain the
house." They clean it for three
years. The kids come around once.  Once a
month later, they come back to the
house, they get
tired of it, then suddenly there are no more
kids
there. I've been
raising kids for years,
others have passed through, 20 years of
working, and one morning they
wake up, I'm not doing what I
want to
do, the kids have left
home. Suddenly they find themselves with all
this
free time, and I'm going to do it. Good luck to
human beings. We like to
be
busy, human beings like
a
challenge, human beings like to
do things that have
meaning. If you're a
mother, if you have children, you feel happy
because someone
needs you and you can serve someone.
If we have purpose in our
lives, we are
happy. The most
unhappy people might be the rich ones, they don't
have
kids, they're sitting at
home and have
time and aren't helping
anyone.
There's
one woman who helps me, her father, I
think, is one of the
richest men in the
world, and this woman gives us money, she gives me
money for the projects I
have. We help many
refugees, she gives a lot of money
for these
projects. One day she called me in New York, she
told me to come to her house. I
went to her house, she was in
bed, it was about 4 in the
afternoon. "Why are you in
bed?" she asked me.  I have no reason to
get up, I have nothing to
do. If I want something, I call
or have it brought to me.
Anything I want, they bring it to me. I
have absolutely nothing to
do. At
that moment, she was the most
unhappy person I
knew. Because we want to have something to
do, we want something that requires a
lot of
thought, we want
something, we want something that is
fun. Doing whatever it is, I
went to a
concert, a concert by a flautist
named [name omitted], he's from
India, and this man started playing the
flute so
beautifully, so
incredibly, and I said, well, I'm going to quit all
my other jobs. I want to learn to
play the flute.
So I went up to him and said,
please teach me the
flute. He studied all the [unclear]
and really loves what he
does. But some people say, "I never
found anything I love to
do."
Friends, friends who have a passion, it could
be yoga, it could be
music, it could be a company, a
business, it could be writing, being a writer,
an
artist. Sometimes you can find something you
really enjoy
doing and you stay up all night
doing
it. This happens to me
sometimes. I'm doing something I love.
I like to translate old texts.
Tibetans or I like to write
books so I start to
[Music]
write and around 9 at
night and suddenly there's some light
outside I thought maybe there's an emergency
in the city something happened so I go to the
window the sun is
coming up I look at the clock I've been here for 6 hours
hours it's like I love doing
this has happened to you too I
know with your first
boyfriend or your first
girlfriend you're
kissing them and suddenly the sun comes out
and like six hours have passed
that's like a type of meditation In
fact when you're 16 and you're kissing
someone it's a
special meditation because you're not thinking about
anything
else When I was young there was a
special movie theater that was outside the drive-in theater, like a
drive-in and mom would take us there it was
cheaper you park the car in the
back there were four of us
siblings and mom would put a kind of
mattress in the
car and at home she had already
[Music]
in the car there we had
a box that had like a
speaker it's
not a
place I started watching the
movie The
Bride and  I hear the
window, there's
someone touching the
window, I lower the
window, it's
[Music]
the 200 cars are
gone, it's 4 in the
morning, we have to close the
movie theater, for
hours you spend
kissing, time flies like that.
That's
passion. You love doing
that.
The purpose of this two-
day talk and the purpose of the
three-
day retreat is going to be to
teach you how to find what you love to do. It does
n't matter how old you
are. Maybe you're
20, maybe you're
60, but you should find what you love to
do.
It's terrible to spend your whole
life going to sleep at 7 in
the
[Music]
afternoon because there's nothing interesting you
want to
do. You're
tired, you worked all
day or at a job you don't love, you
get
home and you don't even like being at
home. That's why people have the
TV remote because they don't even enjoy
TV, they like to push the
button. Maybe I'll find something I like,
but I don't really like anything, I'm
not enjoying
[Music]
TV.  They're watching television
because there's nothing else to do.
So the reason for having this
conference is that we can find what it is that we
love, what we
love in the
monastery. We want
all the people in the
world to
look at page one.
This word here in Tibetan on
page one is
a very difficult word to
describe. It's like
silver inside the
mountain when you dig the
[Music]
mountain, like the veins, the silver,
silver metal,
silver, which is like it has a shape
[Music]. This is the
meaning of the name of our
country. This silver that goes through the
mountain. In Buddhism,
we say that each person has something inside them,
something to
do, and they have to be like a
miner to find that
silver. There are people who never
find it in their whole life. They don't find
their [Music]. They don't find
what they love
[Music] to
do. They don't find what will
keep them up all night, like
the drive-in movie
theater. They never
find it. The purpose of these
talks and the purpose of the
retreat is to help you find
this.
There are many people here
who
meditate, who have an interesting life
[Music].
The to do what you're doing
[Music]
now I was called by a
special name, special names,
Deere
dec,
jati eyes means
rooster because they have those
red eyes. Every night I would stay up
until 3 or 4 in the morning
translating because I love
translating and I would forget to
sleep. So you have a
c, there's something inside you like silver.
If
you find it, your life is going to be so
exciting. You don't have time to
sleep. You don't want to go to
sleep. This
week let's
find it. Each of us has to find it. It's what you do. That's what brought
me closer.
I found
my, for example, I'm a
musician. I love
music. All day, all night I'm
thinking about
music, but I think about something
higher. I'm supposed to do
something more
important. I'm a very good
musician. Last week I was in
Lima and I received an email from
someone who said in the
talk you
said we were going to
learn how to save the
world. How can I help the whole
[Music]
world? And when you said those
words, like a shudder, a
chill. When I was 16
years old, I was walking down the
street and I heard the words resonate in
my
Oh, you're going to save the
world, and since then I hadn't
thought about
that. This person was very happy about
this, and I wrote an email to them
yesterday from
Lima. You said the same
words.
[Music]
esr and I agree when I was
Jen. I listened.
[Music]
palal a no Gar do let's
listen about
Jesus. [
Music]
well, it's like he came to this
world from
heaven, that he had a
mission, then he does a great thing in the
world. My friends and I were
[Music]
talking about all the systems of
government in the
West, all the
businesses, all the culture in the
West. I saw from the
Bible all those
ideas:
democracy,
human rights. These
ideas come from
Jesus. Even if you're not Christian, it doesn't
matter. The
ideas, what Jesus
taught, spread throughout the
world: the idea of ​​voting,
the idea that all opinions of
all people are equal and
important. All this you can
find in
Jesus at the very end, at the very end.
And we all want to be like that. They
make
movies like Spider-Man,
Iron Man,
Superman, Wonder Woman.
[Music]
Transformers, created by the
TR.
That guy already saved the world.  Three
times in all the movies he makes, he has to
come back and save the
world, and we love those
movies. We want them to keep making four.
[Music]
Hollywood loves having more
because they make more
money. Because a lot of people go to see those
movies. Why do we love those movies?
He's a normal guy, he does
three
things: he has a really nice
car, he has the prettiest girl ever,
and he saves the
world. I think those three are
good. We'd like that. We
want to do something that helps everyone. All of
us. I think we want two
things. We want to find what we
love to do
that's going to be interesting and
exciting for
us. And I'm talking to all of
you in this room. I
also have an
interesting life. I travel all the
time.
[Music]
Thousands of
wonderful friends. But there's something else. Are
even you guys who travel
with me doing what you love? Have you
finished your
life and what do you want to
do? All the
time, I know you're changing the
world in the way you're able to. That's why we're
here this
week. Let's find what you love to
do and let's find something that can
help everyone.
We like Jesus. We
want to be like Jesus. We
want  Change the
world this week, learn, we're going to do, it
matters, it's supposed to be to
eat and sleep and
die. You came to this
country right now, it's
supposed to be that you have to do
something, to
do this in half an
hour. 300 people will
die. I can
do it. In our case, it's like we
lost the
message. I have to do something.
Salar, do you feel like that?
Sometimes I think you are
special. You were born for something. There's
a reason why you were born
here, and you were supposed to do
something. You're like on a
mission. Who's the boss? We don't
know, but you're supposed to
do something
special. You're not supposed to be here to
work all day on a computer. There's no
reason. There's supposed to be something
important. The purpose of this
week is for you to
find it. The
message you're supposed to
do is my
goal. I can
show you. If you listen
carefully, you'll see that with time.
There's a
method
to find what you're supposed to
do, and I'll tell you
in these two
days and at the retreat.
Ideas, I can
teach you something
simple: what to
do, and you'll find what you
truly love to do,
and you'll save the
world, you'll change the
world. Millions of
people... [Music] I'm
not supposed to be able to say this, but
we had a great
interview.
That's my
dream, to have the opportunity to talk to
someone like that.
Many readers,
many leaders were
there.
[Music]
There
we can change the conditions for 40
million
people. It's possible we can change
the
conditions. They have to think like this.
You were supposed to do this. I
can
teach you. If you work hard this
week, you can have an interview like the one we
had
today. There are no accidents, no
mistakes. You can sow your
future, you can design your
future. You can change your
country and the
world. You have the
ability. Someone has to show you
where it
is. That's what we're going to
do. We're going to take a
break.
Said 10:15, is if you want to...
on at least 10
minutes,
so I say... All the teachers, please
come up.
[Music]
We're starting
again. Some people asked me a
question during the
break. They told me that this program...
end of  This week is level
two, but if I didn't do level
one,
I'll understand the level in the
retreat. You don't have to worry about
that. Level one and two, we're going to
mix the levels. The level is
separate.
[Music]
Minutes is...
a dog is walking over
here. A dog is coming.
[Music]
Walking
pears. Dog,
can you say something to
chew on? The second question is, who
is
right, the human or the
dog? Can you say
both? The dog can
chew. The human can
write. Both are right. There was
only one person in
Florida, an American, 8 years ago,
was sitting like this. It's
not a
pen. The dog is ruining the
pen. No, the dog says, "The human is
missing the opportunity to chew on
something." It's both things. Next
question: If I put this thing down here
and all the people leave,
all the dogs leave
at that
moment. Is it a pen or something to
chew on? It's... well,
say...
[Music]
Nothing. It's a
thing. If... hand... this... up here...
I see the pen. Does this come from me or
from the pen? Which side is it coming from? It
must be coming from
me. If...  The pen is coming from its
own
side. Then the dog would try to
write with
it, but it doesn't try to write; it comes from
my mind.
There is something in my
mind that causes me to see a
pen. If I close my
eyes and
wish it were
gold, it's not a
pen. If it comes from
me, it would
change; it's still a
pen. This is very important. It
comes from
me, but I have no
control. There is a seed in my
mind that forces me to see the pen. I don't
have a
choice. Who put that seed in my
mind? If you want to plant a
seed, you have to plant it with another
person. You can't plant a seed by yourself; it
's
impossible. To plant a seed in the
mind, you need another
person. So I have to find
someone who wants the same thing I
want. So let's say Carola
needs a
pen. I'm happy to have found her
because now I can plant
one. So I say, "I want to give you a
pen." I put the pen in her
hand. My
mind is watching my hand when I
let it
go. It plants a seed in my mind. It's
very
interesting, an impression on my mind.
A week
later, I go to a
talk. "Ha so
is this thing?"
I see a
pen because I have a seed in my
mind. Who put the
seed
there? I did, because I gave it a
pen. When I give it the
pen, it puts a seed in my
mind. How the seed opens is very
interesting, and we're going to learn more
about this this weekend.
A week
later, at that
moment, the seed opens in my
mind. The
pen comes out. It's this small. It's
an
image. It's an image
of the
seed in my mind.  It gives my
mind a chance and it goes into this thing and I see
a pen. It's so
fast you don't
understand. The dog has a
different seed because it sees an object to
chew on. That seed opens up in the
dog's mind, a tiny image,
a
luminous image in the
mind. It comes to this thing in a
second. If you meditate a lot, you can capture
this
moment. You can see that all the people
in the room come into existence in this
same way. It's very
interesting. You can use this to
make
[Music]
money. That's level A.
If you want to have
[Music]
money today, someone in the government
told me, "I don't need 200 million
dollars, I just want enough to
be
comfortable." I call it
oxygen money. We're all breathing oxygen
in this
room. You're not worried about
breathing too much. You're
not fighting with Hector for more
oxygen because you take it for
granted that you have
oxygen. It's
automatic. You walk around, you're here, you're
breathing. Your whole life is like this, and you don't realize it. It
comes, it's
free, it reaches all
people. If you plant seeds, money
comes to
you like
oxygen. I call it
oxygen money. No, no, it  I pay close attention to
my
bank account. I have someone who takes
care of my
finances. Sometimes I want to do a
new project, I send them an
email. I have enough money to do
this
project, and I tell myself, "I have enough,"
and I
do it. I have no idea how much I have in the
bank. For me, money is like oxygen.
[Music] Here
comes level one. I don't mean to say you have to
make 200 million dollars. If
that doesn't interest you, that's
okay. Someone told me, "I don't want 200
million, then make money, oxygen."
Learn to sow money and
relax. In the days, in times
past, when you wanted some
rice, you had to go walking up the
mountain and look for
rice. Maybe you'd find some
rice, maybe
not. Nowadays,
in the
modern world, Buenos Aires, in all the
cities, they are looking for
money. They get
up, they leave their
homes, they are looking for
money in other
offices and
meetings. They are looking for
money. Sometimes you succeed, sometimes you do
n't. If you know how to sow
seeds, then
in the
old system, the old system seems like
the time of the
cavemen, walking around in the
mountains trying to find a
rice plant. In the new  The
system you're going to learn these
days is simply about planting it.
You don't walk around looking for
money; it
will
grow. Nobody plants a watermelon and then just stares at it. You
plant the
watermelon and then go
home, and after a month you come back and it's
growing. The money is the
same. That's level
one. If you didn't go to level
one, talk to Carola and they'll
teach you level one. They'll
teach you level one again.
What are we talking about
today?
Passion, the secret money that's inside
you, what you love to do. Don't go
looking for
this. Don't go to the
internet. Don't go to the newspapers to
look for
this. Don't pay some university
to take your
money. Simply
plant it. Plant it. We
have 20 more minutes or something like that. We're going
to start tonight.
We're going to do half tonight and
half
tomorrow. How to plant
your
passion. Level one is
money. Level one is
love. Level one is that. Let's go
to the
[Music]
page.
To find your
passion, don't spend the rest of your life
doing something you don't love doing.
Find what you love doing. Do
n't spend the rest of your life
doing something you don't love doing.  It's helping the
whole world. You can do something that helps the
whole world. That's what you were born into. You were supposed to
do something
to change the
world. You can find that. There are four
steps. These four steps you
can also use to make
money. Or, for example, if you're having
problems in your
company
because the workers, the employees,
aren't cooperating with each other,
there are many
strikes, you can change that too. In my
company, I never had a strike in 15
years,
nothing. Just by following these four steps. Let's start tonight and tomorrow we continue.
Step
one: Say
a prayer. What do you want? You can do anything. I want a million
[something]. I want all the [something] in my company. I want to
[something] ...
Carefully, it has to be someone who
wants what you
want. For example, if you want a
pen,
you have to find another person who
needs a pen and give them the
pen. If you don't want strikes in your
company, find a friend, someone
who has another
company that has a
problem, the employees are on
strike, help your friend.
It's very
rare. When you have problems, you
're always thinking about yourself.
In this
system, you have to find another
person who wants the same thing you want, who
has the same
problem, and you have to help that
person. My
suggestion is to take them to Starbucks, to
a coffee shop.
This is good for the
American economy. It's the great American company.
[Music]
Your problem, and
help them. When you're
talking at
Starbucks, it's the same as when you give the
pen. This plants a seed in your
mind. I have a question to ask
you: if you want
money, you have to find a person
who needs
money. If you want a
boyfriend, you need to find a person
who needs a boyfriend.
[Applause]
If you don't know what to do with your
life, you have to find  A
person who doesn't know what to do with their
life—these people aren't hard to
find. You
have to find one of
these
people if you want to find your
hidden talent. You have to find someone who
has this issue, and you must
help them. Jesus said the
same thing: you reap what you
sow. Give to others what you want to
obtain. In our tradition,
we believe the
same, but there are more
details. In our tradition, there are
step-by-step details on how to do
[Music]
this. You can take these
details and
use them with your old system. It's okay to
continue in your old
system. What Jesus said is true, and it's
wonderful. It's beautiful. Now you can have
more information on how to do what
Jesus said. So, I want to find my
passion. Step number
two: you have to find another
person who needs to find their
passion. You can do this in
meditation. For
example, [Music] some people think that
meditating is closing your
eyes, crossing your legs,
too. People think that's how it is.
This is
meditating: not thinking about
anything,
empty mind. It's all an
[Laughter]
illusion. You don't have to do that. You can do
step number
two. We're going to do it tonight. It's going to be
the last thing we do. I'm
going to teach you the  Meditation,
step
two, isn't religious. I don't care
what religion
you practice. I teach
Muslims, Jews,
Hindus, Chinese communists—I
teach everyone. I do
n't care.
Learn the meditation and
do it. Tomorrow we're going to do step three
and step
four. On TV in the
United States, they have
adventure shows. At the end of the
show, they tell you, as they
say, "To be continued." Tomorrow
you can find out who killed the
guy. I'm also doing this
trick. You have to come back tomorrow for
step three and
four, but tonight,
lastly, we're going to do step
two. Carola and Thá have been studying these
things for many
years. I don't come to Buenos Aires very often
because they have them; they do
n't need me as much.
In other countries, there's
nobody. She's going to teach us this meditation
tonight, and if you have more
questions in the coming
months,
contact us, and they'll teach you
more. Let's meditate. If you don't have anything
bothering you, close your
eyes and slowly become very
still. Perceive your body from
head to
toe and release the
body
at the same time as you
breathe.  Exhaling and
inhaling through your
nose. Look at the tip of your
nose. Watch the air go
out. Feel the air go out
and watch it and feel it go in without forcing
anything, like a
concentration exercise. Every time you get distracted, go
back to that
exercise,
exhaling and inhaling.
And now we're going to start our
exercise. First, you have to have
your prayer, at least for tonight.
Clearly state what you
want, talking about your
passion. What moment in your life
are you in? We remember the situations of the
young person who is facing the end of
their career and doesn't know what they want to
do, or maybe you've been
working on something for years and suddenly you
wake up one day and say, "What am I
doing? Why was I born?
What is the meaning of this
life?" Maybe you find yourself with more time
because your children have left home or
something like that has happened, and you ask yourself the same
question. Put together a prayer regarding
your
passion: I want to find passion in my
life. I want to find something I truly
love to do, something in which I
completely lose myself, in which I lose all
sense of
time, all sense of limitation. The self
dissolves when I am doing
this
activity; it's as if my  Heart
expands beyond
known limits.
I want to find the silver beta at the
center of my
heart. That would be step
one. Now I invite you to
search your
mind for someone you
know, someone very real, someone who
has a name and surname for
you, who is in the same situation as
you. If many people appear,
please choose
one. What do they
need? What's wrong with them? Try
to identify that person's need.
[Music]
Clearly, they are also finding the
meaning of life. They know they were born for
something more
important, but they lost that
message. They are searching for it, just like
you.
And now you are going to make a
plan. Start mentally creating a plan
of how you are going to talk to that person. You are going to
take them to a
café, some place like Starbucks or
some small café,
to chat for a
while. I want you to visualize all of this: the
moment you call this
person, you invite them, you
agree on where you are going
to
meet.
And be very clear about where you are going to
meet mentally. Give me an
address. Give me a time, a
date. And now, mentally, go to the
meeting.
You meet the
person and you sit down to
chat.  You have to help this
person find their passion in
life in some skillful way. You're going to
try to
help them, maybe be direct and say, "
You have a problem, you're lost, I
have to help you." That might not be the most
skillful way. Consider how
you could talk about this
topic. Now I'm going to leave you
in silence for a few minutes while you imagine the
conversation.
If you mentally go somewhere else, to another
time, gently bring yourself back with
your breath to this visualization you
're doing. I want you to feel it very
real. Imagine the place, the sensations, the
sounds of the
place, the
aromas, everything you see, the colors, the
people there. You are in that
place talking to
that
person. Start
now with
the first encounter. Maybe it's very
simple, very short, a few
suggestions, ideas come and
go. The encounter is about to end,
and you plan the next
one. And in your mind, every day
until the next encounter, you keep this
in some corner of your mind. You remember
this
person, you wonder how they're doing, you
send them an email to
continue these ideas, this
conversation. You have this person in your
mind, in your heart,
present every
day as if you were...  Cultivating a
plant, a beautiful
flower, every day you pass by it, you look at it, you water it, you move it
closer to or further from the
Light with great patience and with great
love, slowly, breathe deeply several
times,
relax your body, and when you are ready
you can open your
eyes. The teachers will be
here if you have any questions after what we have already discussed.